So hey guys, today I'm
going to showcase this
browser agent that I built
in OE1.
So what is this
tool? So this is a
tool that does tasks on
the behalf of the user
automatically.
So let's get into the
demo, shall we?
So here is the dashboard
page where we can instruct
the agent what
we
want it to do.
First, I'll give it a
very simple task to go
to
Google
and search for today's NVIDIA
prize.
Right, so let's see what
happens. So I hit enter,
and then
the agent will start. So
it just went and showed
me this one. And here,
it is showing me what
it is doing at the
moment.
So yeah, and the objective
is done, and now it
won't do anything else. So
this is
a very simple task. Now,
let me refresh this one
more time.
So
now let me ask it
to
do a little bit more
complex. So
go to YouTube
and play the latest video
from the channel
OpenAI.
This is a little bit
more complex task,
but
it should be able to
do this one as well.
So let's see what it
does. It first went to
YouTube directly in the OpenAI
channel.
Now,
let's see what it does.
So yeah, it just
played the
latest video from OpenAI.
Let me pause the video.
So it is done and
the image is playing and
it stopped.
So yeah, this is the
browser agent.
And I hope you like
it. So have a good
day.
Bye.